<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>asn - Anton Stepan</title>
    <link>https://asndev.github.io/tags/go/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on asn - Anton Stepan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://asndev.github.io/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Foobar for real</title>
      <link>https://asndev.github.io/post/2016/foobar-for-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asndev.github.io/post/2016/foobar-for-real/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1-install-hugo&#34;&gt;Step 1. Install Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go Gopher!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about es6?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;const letterCapitalize = (input) =&amp;gt; {
  return input.split(&#39; &#39;)
    .map((word) =&amp;gt; {
      return word.charAt(0)
        .toUpperCase() + word.slice(1);
    })
    .join(&#39; &#39;);
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nap all day. Sit in box kitty power! stare at ceiling light rub face on everything lies down . Who&amp;rsquo;s the baby. Knock dish off table head butt cant eat out of my own dish jump around on couch, meow constantly until given food, or poop in litter box, scratch the walls catch mouse and gave it as a present groom yourself 4 hours - checked, have your beauty sleep 18 hours - checked, be fabulous for the rest of the day - checked!. Human give me attention meow i am the best. Loves cheeseburgers run outside as soon as door open and find something else more interesting, meowing non stop for food, white cat sleeps on a black shirt for lie on your belly and purr when you are asleep. Hola te quiero swat turds around the house sleep on keyboard, yet eat prawns daintily with a claw then lick paws clean wash down prawns with a lap of carnation milk then retire to the warmest spot on the couch to claw at the fabric before taking a catnap. Climb leg why must they do that give attitude, yet when in doubt, wash cats go for world domination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>